[
  {
    "id": "133",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which data preparation technique involves converting categorical values into numeric values using mappings and one-hot techniques",
      "answers": [
        "categorical encoding",
        "feature engineering",
        "handling missing values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["categorical encoding"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "134",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which data preparation technique involves transforming features so they are ready for ML algorithms",
      "answers": [
        "categorical encoding",
        "feature engineering",
        "handling missing values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["feature engineering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "135",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which data preparation technique involves ensuring the relevant features are used for the problem at hand",
      "answers": [
        "categorical encoding",
        "feature engineering",
        "handling missing values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["feature engineering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "136",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which data preparation technique involves removing incomplete, incorrectly formatted, irrelevant or duplicated data",
      "answers": [
        "categorical encoding",
        "feature engineering",
        "handling missing values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["handling missing values"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "137",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is a tool to use for ad-hoc cleaning and transforming?",
      "answers": [
        "SageMaker and jupyter notebook",
        "ETL jobs in AWS Glue",
        "SparkML",
        "SageMaker Neo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker and jupyter notebook"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "138",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is a tool to use for reusable transformation and cleaning?",
      "answers": [
        "SageMaker and jupyter notebook",
        "ETL jobs in AWS Glue",
        "SparkML",
        "SageMaker Neo"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["ETL jobs in AWS Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The process of manipulating categorical values when ML algorithms expect numerical values as inputs",
      "answers": [
        "categorical encoding",
        "feature engineering",
        "handling missing values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["categorical encoding"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A categorical feature is a ______",
      "answers": [
        "discrete feature",
        "indiscreet feature",
        "continuous feature",
        "numerical feature"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["discrete feature"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "140",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When predicting the price of a home you should use the ______ algorithm and encoding is ______",
      "answers": [
        "Linear Regression, necessary",
        "Naive Bayes, not necessary",
        "Convolutional Network, necessary",
        "Convolutional Network, not necessary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Linear Regression, necessary"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "141",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When determining whether a given text is about sports or not you should use the ______ algorithm and encoding is ______",
      "answers": [
        "Linear Regression, necessary",
        "Naive Bayes, not necessary",
        "Convolutional Network, necessary",
        "Convolutional Network, not necessary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Naive Bayes, not necessary"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "142",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When detecting malignancy is radiology images or not you should use the ______ algorithm and encoding is ______",
      "answers": [
        "Linear Regression, necessary",
        "Naive Bayes, not necessary",
        "Convolutional Network, necessary",
        "Convolutional Network, not necessary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Convolutional Network, necessary"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "143",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When using the term ordinal",
      "answers": [
        "order matters, for example large > medium > small",
        "order is immaterial",
        "order does not matter, for example blue, green, red",
        "order is random"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["order matters, for example large > medium > small"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "144",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When using the term nominal",
      "answers": [
        "order matters, for example large > medium > small",
        "order is immaterial",
        "order does not matter, for example blue, green, red",
        "order is random"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["order does not matter, for example blue, green, red"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "145",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When encoding nominal values use ______",
      "answers": [
        "one-hot-encoding",
        "imputation",
        "binning",
        "feature splits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["one-hot-encoding"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "146",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ transforms nominal categorical features and creates new binary columns for each observation",
      "answers": [
        "one-hot-encoding",
        "imputation",
        "binning",
        "feature splits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["one-hot-encoding"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "147",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ adds columns to your data set (one for each encoded feature) containing 1s and 0s",
      "answers": [
        "one-hot-encoding",
        "imputation",
        "binning",
        "feature splits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["one-hot-encoding"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "148",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ is not always a good choice when there are many categories to encode",
      "answers": [
        "one-hot-encoding",
        "imputation",
        "binning",
        "feature splits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["one-hot-encoding"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "149",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Using techniques like ______ by similarity could create fewer overall categories before encoding",
      "answers": [
        "grouping",
        "imputation",
        "binning",
        "feature splits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["grouping"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "150",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Mapping ______ to ‘other’ can help reduce the overall number of new columns created",
      "answers": [
        "rare values",
        "repeating",
        "unique",
        "common values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["rare values"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "151",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique tokenizes raw text and creates a statistical representation of the text",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Bag-of-Words"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "152",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique is an extension of Bag-of-Words which produces groups of words of n size",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["N-Gram"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "153",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique breaks up text by white space into groups of words",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["N-Gram"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "154",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique creates groups of words of size n and outputs every pair of words that includes the first word",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "155",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique creates groups of words that always include the first word",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "156",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique represents how important a word or words are to a given set of text by providing appropriate weights to terms that are common and less common",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "157",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text feature engineering technique shows us the popularity of a word or words in text data by making common words like the or and less important",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "158",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When matching phrases in spam emails, use the ______ text transformation",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["N-Gram"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "159",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation makes it easier to compare phrases like click here now or you are a winner?",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["N-Gram"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "160",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "When determining the subject matter of multiple PDFs, use the ______ or ______ text transformation",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
      "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "161",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation filters less important words in PDFs?",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "162",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation helps you find common word combinations repeated throughout PDFs?",
      "answers": [
        "Bag-of-Words",
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "163",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "To determine the subject matter of multiple PDFs, which of these would you do to find subject of each document?",
      "answers": [
        "first use tf-idf to filter out less important words through the PDFs",
        "then use orthogonal sparse bigram to find common word combinations that are repeated throughout the PDFs",
        "first use orthogonal sparse bigram to find common word combinations that are repeated throughout the PDFs",
        "then use tf-idf to filter out less important words through the PDFs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["first use tf-idf to filter out less important words through the PDFs",
        "then use orthogonal sparse bigram to find common word combinations that are repeated throughout the PDFs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "164",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique creates a new feature from the combination of two or more text or categorical values?",
      "answers": [
        "cartesian product transformation",
        "cartesian tree transformation",
        "cartesian oval transformation",
        "cartesian morphism transformation"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["cartesian product transformation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "165",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique combines sets of words together?",
      "answers": [
        "cartesian product transformation",
        "cartesian tree transformation",
        "cartesian oval transformation",
        "cartesian morphism transformation"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["cartesian product transformation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "166",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique splits text by whitespace with a window size of n?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["N-Gram"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "167",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique splits text by keeping first word and uses delimeter with remaining whitespaces between second word with window size n?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "168",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique helps us determine how important words are within multiple documents?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "169",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique removes punctuation from text?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["removing punctuation"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "170",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique lowercase all words in the text?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["lowercase"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "171",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique combines words together to create a new feature?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["cartesian product"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "172",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Engineering",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which text transformation technique extracts information from dates and creates new features?",
      "answers": [
        "N-Gram",
        "Orthogonal Sparse Bigram (OSB)",
        "Term Frequency-Inverse Document Frequency (tf-idf)",
        "removing punctuation",
        "lowercase",
        "cartesian product",
        "feature engineering dates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["feature engineering dates"]
    }
  }
]